[Music]
Mr. Jain, we were already talking about a lot of buzzing stocks today.
So the first name is
Ireda where the numbers came.   The
reaction after the numbers is good and everything is
going on by discounting the negative and positive things.  What should be done in this?
Sir, level 178 has been reached in Ed.  Here,
if you are an extreme short term trader, book 50%
profit.  Do 50% on 187.
If you are an investor, then the last
volume that came on March 24, which was a 450% rise, is
its follow-through move today.  Again the volume
is up 500%.  So this shows that
institutional accumulation has become very strong.  The
stock should make a slow and steady move up to at least 235.  It can take
six months for Ada
because it is a low beta counter and
will move slowly but the treasury has already gone up.
We came across ICICI LBD numbers and
although profits fell by around 9.12%, the
gross premium increased and the share is up by 1.5%.
And like wise ICICI PDL's numbers also
came.  The numbers there also
showed a decline in APE but it appeared to be
slightly inline with the expectations and coming on the lesser side.  The
reaction here
is also positive.  So what should one do with these three insurance stocks - ICICI Prudential, ICICI
LBRD and HDFC Ltd
?  And Sir ICICI
potential particularly 691 means
average volume is 691000.  Today the
volume is 2 million but the range is of inside bar and the
previous day range has been crossed.  So
this creates a little doubt.  But as per the
structure, it seems to be going towards ₹153.
And the rest of these life insurance companies
or insurance companies, the
momentum is slightly higher in all of them.  HDFC Bank has a
very good structure.  So if I had to choose
one from all, my
top pick would be HDFC Life.  Second best would have been ICICI
Pall.  Apart from this, we have a Jasol
Engineering which has been very famous.  It was
necessary to talk about that since yesterday evening.  Jain
Saheb Jasol Engineering A might be the
first example for the people after Covid.
But there are many names
who have eroded 90% of the wealth.  If
you want to count the names, then Pujalid will also come in it
, GTL will also come, GTL Infra will also come or at
one time the companies of Reliance ADAG Group will
also come in it.  So the market has seen this kind of situation
before.
This might be an old thing for you and me.  But
for many people it will be their first accident.
So how to read such stocks
?
Look sir, in this I would like to say one thing that
James for Engineering did not give you a
chance to leave.  When the buying
climax happened and it was falling, then
we discussed multiple times that the buying
climax has happened, get out, there is a 50% chance that it will
fall by 80%, there is an 80% chance that it will fall by 50%, so
you will get out somewhere, the news may have just come
but you have been getting evidence on the charts for a long time that you
should get out, selling of smart money is
visible, now this incident has happened to you for the first
time, make it a lesson and remember this thing
that next time, wherever you go, you have mid cap and
small cap.  If your buying has caused a
drop of more than 8%, then exit immediately.
Invest in some other stock.
So this is the bottom line, if you learn from this then
you will earn a lot of money in the stock market.
Ok.  Apart from this, Mahanagar Gas and
see here the allocation due to the impact of cut from GAIL has been
reduced by around 18%.
So its impact has been felt in IGL as well as
in Mahanagar Gas.  IGL has a
little bit but Mahanagar is big in gas.  There
is a 4.5% drop.  How are you reading
it?  Sir, this is the last time when it dropped twice with a gap.  The
results were also bad and the
last time
news of this cut came was in October.  The stock never recovered after that.  There
is definitely an upmove on the weekly chart from the major support of 1168
but on the weekly it seems that a bearish flag
kind of pattern has formed.  If
₹1205 is broken during this period of bad news, then a
big downside will open at ₹954.  If you have it right now,
hold it.  The stock will be bad only below ₹15.
As long as it is above that, it will remain
in the range 120 1384, so either
you can get the review done at 1384 or get it done around 1200.  At
the moment it is absolutely
within range.  So it can continue in this range.
We are within a limit and can
continue only within the limit.
But today there is news flow and
due to news flow pressure was seen here.
So these are all the shares where there was news, there was a
trigger and between which
reactions were seen coming here today.  So for now let's
wrap up the buzzing stock here.
[music]